altestore.com 2019-03-10

# Privacy Policy | altE

altE is the sole owner of information collected on this site. We will not sell, share, or rent this information to any outside parties, except as outlined in this policy. We collect information from our customers to process orders and better serve you with pertinent information, such as order confirmations and order status updates. Information collected includes your name, shipping address, billing address, telephone numbers, e-mail address, and payment information such as your credit card number. We also require you to submit a username and password of your choice for your future access to your account information. To safeguard that your user name and password remain confidential, DO NOT share this information with anyone. If you elect to receive our newsletter or special promotions, your contact information will be used for the delivery of these items. 

We allow third-party companies to collect non-personally identifiable information when customers visit our site. These companies typically use a cookie to collect this information in order to provide understand the usage of the altE website so we can further optimize the experience in the future. Our site does not respond to “Do Not Track” signals or mechanisms. In addition, other parties who perform data analytics for altE, such as Google Analytics, may collect personally identifiable information about your online activities when you use our Services. You can opt-out of Analytics for altE's website by following the instructions [here](https://support.google.com/analytics/answer/181881?hl=en). 

## Registration

In order to process your orders placed on this website, you must first complete the registration form. During registration, you will be required to provide your contact information, which includes your name, e-mail address, telephone number and street address. This information is used to provide you with important altE services such as automated order status updates via e-mail.

## Order

Most of the data collected in the registration process will be used to process orders. During the order process, you will have to provide financial information such as your credit card number, expiration date, money order, wire transfer or check information. This information is used for billing purposes and to fulfill your order. If we have trouble processing an order, we will use this contact information to get in touch with you. To properly process your credit card information, we must share your personal and financial information with the merchant bank for authorization and approval. This process is protected by an enhanced security system. See the Security section below for more details on security measures and procedures. We do not share your personal and financial information with any third parties, except those specified in the Sharing section of this policy.

## Cookies

We customize certain Web page content based upon your browser type and other information provided by our cookie. If you choose to reject the cookie, you can still browse our store but will be unable to use the shopping cart to buy merchandise. You can, however, place your order over the phone line with one of our technical sales representatives by calling +1(877) 878-4060. The altE shopping cart cannot function without cookies enabled so that the necessary information to process your order is retained. If you disable cookies, altE's website will be unable to accept your online order. We will not share any personally identifiable information provided by this cookie with any third party.

## Log Files

We use IP addresses to analyze trends, administer the site, track user movement, and gather broad demographic information for aggregate use. 

## Sharing

We may employ third party companies to perform functions on our behalf. These functions may include order fulfillment, package delivery, marketing assistance, postal and e-mail delivery, customer service, data analysis, and credit processing. The third parties we contract for these purposes have limited access to your personal information and may not use it for other purposes.

For wholesale customers (i.e. altE Direct customers) we may also share relevant sales data with supplying manufacturers for understanding location of installations the manufacturer's products.

We reserve the right to disclose your personally identifiable information as required by law, and when we believe that disclosure is necessary to protect our rights and/or comply with a judicial proceeding, court order, or legal process served on our website.

## Testimonials

The testimonials section of the altE website is for the purpose of sharing positive experiences. The testimonials section is moderated to ensure accurate and positive testimonials. Published testimonials are genuine and are not edited or altered by altE. altE reserves the right to post or remove any testimonial at its discretion.

By posting your comment(s) or testimonial(s) ("Testimonial") on our website, you give us permission to reprint or use the Testimonial in connection with our business. You also are agreeing to the following: (1) The reprint or use of the Testimonial will be at our discretion and without compensation; (2) We may use the Testimonial with or without any pseudo (pen) name credit; (3) Our right to use the Testimonial is perpetual and may be assigned by us; (4) We may use the Testimonial locally, nationally or globally and such use may be made in any media, information or communication platform (including Internet advertising) currently in use or later developed; and (5) You and not someone else composed and posted the Testimonial.

Other than your pseudo (pen) name, which we may or may not use, your personal contact information will not be disclosed in connection with our reprint or use of your Testimonial.

## Children

altE does not sell products for purchase by children. Youth-oriented products are sold for purchase by adults only. If you are under the age of 18, you may only use altE in the presence of a consenting parent or guardian. We will not knowingly or intentionally collect personal information via the Internet from children under the age of 13. altE is committed to protecting the welfare and privacy of children.

## Links

This website contains links to other sites. Please be aware that altE is not responsible for the privacy practices of such other sites. We encourage our users to be aware when they leave our site, and to read the privacy statements of each and every website that collects personally identifiable information. This privacy statement applies only to information collected by this website.

## Security

altE takes precautions to protect its customers' information. When you submit sensitive information via the website, your information is protected both online and offline.

When our registration/order form asks you to enter sensitive information (such as your credit card number), that information is encrypted and is protected using SSL encryption software. To learn more about SSL, follow this link: [www.verisign.com](http://www.verisign.com/).

altE no longer supports the version 3.0 SSL protocol as of November 6, 2014.  
Please review your browser version to ensure it supports the latest secure protocols.

> Apple Safari: <http://support.apple.com/downloads/#safari>  
>  Google Chrome: <https://www.google.com/chrome/>  
>  Microsoft Internet Explorer: <https://www.microsoft.com/ie/>  
>  Mozilla Firefox: <https://www.getfirefox.com/>  
>  Opera: <https://www.opera.com/>

Access to all of our users' information is restricted. Security cameras are positioned throughout the building in conjunction with multiple alarm systems. Only employees who need the information to perform a specific job are granted access to personally identifiable information. If you wish to have your financial information removed at the time of your order, you may opt to have your financial information deleted from our records upon completion of your order. Otherwise, you may contact by calling toll free +1(877) 878-4060, to request that your information be deleted from our database. For future transactions, you will be required to re-enter your information.

All altE servers, including web servers and database servers, are housed and maintained in secure locations. Access to the database is strictly monitored and protected from outside access. Internet access is restricted and protected by multiple firewalls and password protection. The servers on which we store personally identifiable information are kept in a secured environment, inside a secured and locked room. All backups are stored and locked in a high-level security room. Only personnel with proper security clearance have access to these restricted areas. 

All employees are kept up-to-date on our security and privacy practices. Every quarter, in addition to any time a new policy is added, altE employees are notified and/or reminded about the importance of privacy, and what they can do to ensure that customers' information remains protected at all times.

If you have any questions or concerns about altE's security practices, you can call us toll free at +1(877) 878-4060.

## Special Offers

Our special offers are sent only to customers who grant altE permission to send them such information.

To honor the privacy of our users, we offer the option to not receive these types of communications. At the time of your order, you may opt to not receive special offers and news by clicking the appropriate field. Furthermore, all special offers are sent via e-mail and include an opt-out link if you no longer wish to receive special offers and news. Customers might still receive intermittent updates on products, services, specials or altE news. Please reference the Choice/Opt-out section below for further details on how to be removed from our mailing list should you choose to be removed.

## Correction/Updating/Reviewing Personal Information

Customers may change or review their stored account information such as street address or e-mail address through our website by visiting our Help section. You must have your username and password in order to access your account. In the event you forget both your username and password, please contact our customer service department for assistance.

## Choice/Opt-out

For customers who wish to opt-out and stop receiving altE special offers and related news, altE provides several ways to do so. Users who no longer wish to receive our newsletter or promotional materials may opt-out of receiving these communications by clicking on the unsubscribe link in a recent emailing. They may also send e-mails to marketing@altEstore.com with a request to be removed. 

## Notification of Changes

If we decide to change our Privacy Policy, we will post those changes to this privacy statement, the homepage, and other places we deem appropriate so that you are aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances, if any, we disclose it. We reserve the right to modify this privacy statement at any time, so please review it frequently. If we make material changes to this policy, we will notify you here, by email, or by means of a notice on our homepage.

If you have opted out of receiving communications from altE, you will still be able to view news of policy changes at www.altEstore.com. Otherwise, you may e-mail us at marketing@altEstore.com or call us toll free at +1(877) 878-4060 to ask our customer service department about changes and updates.

## Last Update

The Privacy Policy contained herein became officially effective January 1, 2016.

## Address

altE   
330 Codman Hill Rd  
Boxborough, MA 01719  
USA
